shudoo.co.uk 2011-03-10

# Privacy Policy

**General information**

**Shudoo Accounts**

**Your Consent**

**Communication and Marketing**

**Disclosures of your information**

**Third Party Sites**

**Criteo**

**General Information**

Our privacy policy is very simple - we will NEVER share any information that you give us with a third party except to provide you with better service, where we are required to do so by law, or unless stated otherwise.

You may browse the shudoo.co.uk website without entering your personal details. However, at some stages on the website you may be asked for personal information to enable us to reply to any enquiries and/or process your order.

**Shudoo Accounts**

If you register an account with shudoo.co.uk we keep a record of your personal information including name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and if you place an order, some of your credit card details (i.e. without the CV2 security number). No transactions can take place without the card CV2 number. This information is stored in our database so we may recognise you as a registered customer and to speed up any future orders you place with us.

We also keep a record of your purchases, which enables us to improve our service to our customers. E-mail correspondence is saved so we may track questions or concerns you may have with our products or service.

**Your Consent**

Unlike most other mail-order companies, shudoo.co.uk do not participate in the selling, renting or in any other way sharing of your personal information, including e-mail addresses, with other companies.

**Communication and Marketing**

By entering any one of our competitions then you will be automatically signed up to receive newsletters from Shudoo, as outline in our competition terms and conditions.

You can opt out of receiving Shudoo newsletters by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom left hand corner of any given newsletter.

To discuss removing yourself from our lists, please contact us via the methods stated on our ‘Contact’ page.

**Disclosures of your information**

Any information stored about you by shudoo.co.uk is used only to improve our products and service and we will use your personal information only for:

• Processing orders as effectively as possible  
• Business analysis to make your shopping experience with us in the future as quick & as simple as possible.  
• Providing you with information about our products and services you have requested. shudoo.co.uk will share your personal information only:  
• With service providers who aid us in delivering our products and services to you. This includes:  
• Home Delivery Network and Royal Mail in order to make deliveries.  
• Outside companies who distribute e-mails or products on our behalf.  
• Sagepay (online credit card processing service)

In each instance, we provide them with the minimum amount of information required for them to perform their tasks.

**Third Party Sites**

In various places on our site we may at times link to third party sites. If you follow a link onto such a site, please note that they will adhere to their own privacy policies by which Shudoo holds no responsibility or liability.

**Criteo**

For retargeting activity we work with Criteo. While looking on the shudoo website you allow Criteo to send its own cookies to your cookie file. Criteo will thus collect non-personal data relating to your internet activity; Criteo will collect and use these non-personal data in accordance with all applicable laws and regulations (including but not limited to laws governing privacy and data protection); Criteo's Privacy Policy is available at <http://www.criteo.com/en/solutions/privacy-policy>. Criteo advises information regarding how to opt-out of being cookie retargeted is available on its website.
